interviewexchange.com 2015-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Hirezon HR Software Solutions

Hirezon Corporation, d/b/a Interview Exchange (InterviewExchange) is committed to providing its customers with outstanding service. The Interview Exchange respects the privacy of its on-line users and has constructed and administers this website accordingly.

InterviewExchange product website [www.interviewexchange.com](http://www.interviewexchange.com/) may use ‘cookie’ technology with respect to this site, but makes such use only to obtain non-personal information from on-line users. This information will be used only as necessary to permit functionality of the website or to enhance the user’s on-line experience. For example, we may track the number of visitors using the site in order to improve the site and the manner in which it is used and to develop new features.

InterviewExchange gathers only personally identifiable information, such as name and address, when this information is voluntarily submitted by users. Any and all such information collected by us is used for our business purposes only. We will not allow such collected information to be sold, traded or viewed by any third party. The only exceptions to this policy are when the user gives InterviewExchange his/her consent to share this information; when we need to share such information to provide a service that he/she has requested; or when we are required by law to disclose information. In addition, unless requested, users will not receive e-mail from InterviewExchange as a result of visiting the website. 

InterviewExchange has no intention of accepting information from individuals under the age of 18. If you are not at least 18 years of age, please leave this site immediately. Parents are urged to monitor and supervise their children’s on-line activity. 

InterviewExchange reserves the right to change this policy at any time without prior notice. Please check this page periodically for updates to the policy.

This policy describes the information practices of InterviewExchange in connection with this website [www.interviewexchange.com](http://www.interviewexchange.com/). The policy does not govern websites of other parties to which InterviewExchange may provide links. InterviewExchange does not control and is not responsible for the privacy practices of or the data available on the websites of third parties, and we urge you to evaluate the soundness of these practices and data for yourself.

**Security**  
InterviewExchange takes every precaution to protect user information. When users submit sensitive information via the InterviewExchange website, that information is protected both online and offline. When the InterviewExchange registration form asks users to enter personal or any sensitive information, such as Driver’s License that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry – SSL.

While on a secure pages, the lock icon on any of the standard web browsers such as Mozilla, Chrome, Safari and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just ‘surfing.’ 

To learn more about SSL, follow this link: <http://www.verisign.com/ssl/ssl-information-center/how-ssl-security-works/index.html>. While InterviewExchange uses SSL encryption to protect personal information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user information offline. InterviewExchange strives to protect the privacy of the information we process, and inadvertent disclosure is extremely unlikely. In the event of such an inadvertent disclosure, InterviewExchange will take all commercially reasonable steps to limit and remedy the disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to defeat those procedures or use your personal information for improper purposes.

If you have any questions about the security at the InterviewExchange website [www.interviewexchange.com](http://www.interviewexchange.com/), please contact us by email at[ info@interviewexchange.com](mailto:info@interviewexchange.com)

**Contact Information**  
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding the InterviewExchange privacy policy, please contact us at:  
Hirezon Corporation  
4 Bellows Road,  
Westborough, Massachusetts 01581-0792  
Phone: (508) 836-3800  
Fax: (508) 836-2020  
Email: [info@interviewexchange.com](mailto:info@interviewexchange.com)  
Website:[ http://www.interviewexchange.com ](http://www.interviewexchange.com/)
